Guide to the Alan Farley Collection ARS.0067
Archive of Recorded Sound
Alan Farley Collection
1994-2009
ARS.0067
Archive of Recorded Sound
8.75 linear feet
The Alan Farley Collection consists primarily of recordings made for the radio program Book Talk recorded on audio cassette tapes, digital audio tapes and compact discs. Book Talk airs on KALW 91.7 FM in San Francisco, California, though some of the recordings are used for other radio programs Farley hosts on KALW, such as the show Open Air.
Farley, Alan
Arrangement note
The collection is organized into one series: I. The Alan Farley Collection, and thirteen boxes: I. 1996-1997 Book Talk Episodes. II. 1998 Book Talk Episodes. III. 1999 Book Talk Episodes. IV. 2000 Book Talk Episodes. V. 2001 Book Talk Episodes. VI. 2002 Book Talk Episodes. VII. 2003 Book Talk Episodes. VII. 2004 Book Talk Episodes. IX. 2005 Book Talk Episodes. X. 2006 Book Talk Episodes. XI. 2007 Book Talk Episodes. XII. 2008 Book Talk Episodes. XIII. 2008-2009 Book Talk Episodes.
Biographical/Historical note
Alan Farley is a volunteer producer of talk and music programming at the noncommercial public radio station KALW 91.7 FM in San Francisco, California. He is host and producer for the music show Open Air and the talk show Book Talk, described by KALW's website as, "in-depth interviews with contemporary authors." Additionally, Farley hosts I Love To Rhyme, My Favorite Things and Explorations in Music. Farley has been involved with KALW since 1975. KALW has been broadcasting since March 1941, and was the first FM radio station in San Francisco, as well as the first educational FM station in the United States.
Though the interviews in the collection are sometimes used for other shows, they are recorded for broadcast first on Book Talk. The show has interviewed such authors as Joyce Carol Oates, Isabel Allende, Salman Rushdie, Al Franken, Gore Vidal, John Updike, George Stephanopoulos, Chastity (Chaz) Bono, Mary Higgins Clarke, Michael Ondaatje, Sherman Alexie, Caroline Kennedy, and Armistead Maupin. It is a half hour long show broadcast weekly.
Conditions Governing Access note
Collection is open for research. Listening appointments may require 24 hours notice. Contact the Archive Operations Manager.
Scope and Contents note
The Alan Farley Collection consists of recordings made by Alan Farley for the Book Talk radio program on KALW 91.7 in San Francisco, California. The recordings are on audio cassette tapes, digital audio tapes and compact discs. The recordings are interviews between Alan Farley and numerous local, national and international authors of fiction and nonfiction works.
KALW (Radio station: San Francisco, Calif.); Authors--20th century--Interviews; Radio interviews; Radio talk shows; Radio programs--United States; San Francisco Bay Area (Calif.)
- 1996-1997 Book Talk Episodes, 1995-1997; 32 audio cassette tapes (Audio 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Order of information: Episode Number; Author Last Name, Author First Name; Book Title; [Author Last Name-2, Author First Name-2; Book Title-2;] Record Date; Air Date (Length:Minutes)
  B9633; Posner,Gerald; Citizen Perot; 8/23/1996; 9/8/1996 (:18)
  B9634; Hornby, Nick; High Fidelity; 9/11/1996; 9/15/1996 (:23)
  B9635; Levin, Donna; Get That Novel Written; 9/18/1996; 9/22/1996 (:13)
  B9635; Leavitt, David; Mitchell, Mark; Italian Pleasures; 8/13/1996; 9/22/1996 (:15)
  B9636; Ferguson, Gary; Spirits Of The Wild; 9/23/1996; 9/29/1996 (:14)
  B9636; Glickstein, Lee; Public Speaking; 9/19/1996; 9/29/1996 (:13)
  B9637; Parenti, Michael; Dirty Truths; 8/1/1996; 10/13/1996 (:33)
  B9638; Pratchett, Terry; Feet Of Clay; 10/3/1996; 10/20/1996 (:18)
  B9639; Djerassi, Carl; Marx, Deceased; 10/24/1996; 10/27/1996 (:18)
  B9640: Denby, David; Great Books; 9/26/1996; 11/3/1996 (:21)
  B9641; Wideman, John Edgar; The Cattle Killing; 10/21/1996; 11/10/1996 (:15)
  B9641; Hustvedt, Siri; The Enchantment Of Lili Dahl; 10/8/1996; 11/10/1996 (:14)
  B9642; Bantock, Nick; The Venetian's Wife; 10/7/1996; 11/17/1996 (:14)
  B9642; Vermeij, Geerat; Privileged Hands; 9/30/1996; 11/17/1996 (:13)
  B9643; Church, Forrest; Life Lines; 10/21/1996; 11/24/1996 (:15)
  B9643; Hunt, D. Trinidad; Operating Manual For Planet Earth; Church, Forrest; Life Lines; 10/8/1996; 11/24/1996 (:12)
  B9644; Spence, Gerry; The Making Of A Country Lawyer; 10/28/1996; 12/1/1996 Also Aired 3/10/97 On Open Air (:30)
  B9645; Ellerbe, Helen; The Dark Side of Christian History; 12/5/1996; 12/8/1996 (:09)
  B9645; Cruse, Howard; Stuck Rubber Baby; 10/17/1996; 12/8/1996 (:16)
  B9646; Hoare, Philip; Noel Coward - A Biography; 11/16/1995; 12/15/1996 (:13)
  B9646; Castle, Terry; Noel Coward And Radclyffe Hall - Kindred Spirits; Philip Hoare; Noel Coward - A Biography; 12/9/1996; 12/15/1996 (:16)
  B9647; Schickel, Richard; Clint Eastwood; 12/6/1996; 12/22/1996 (:30)
  B9701; Nesaule, Agate; A Woman In Amber; 1/14/1997; 1/19/1997 (:26)
  B9702; Kolber-Stuart, Billy & Alport, David; Out And About; 1/22/1997; 1/26/1997 (:30)
  B9703; Strauss, Bill; The Fourth Turning; 1/31/1997; 2/2/1997 (:13)
  B9703; Bloom, Amy; Love Invents Us; 1/23/1997; 2/2/1997 (:15)
  B9704; Hillerman, Tony; The Fallen Man; 1/29/1997; 2/9/1997 (:30)
  B9705; Bachardy, Don; Isherwood Diaries, Vol. 1; 2/10/1997; 2/16/1997 (:30)
  B9706; Nakatani, Al & Nakatani, Jane; Honor Thy Children; 2/14/1997; 2/23/1997 (:25)
  B9707; Irving, John; Trying To Save Piggy Sneed; 2/19/1997; 3/2/1997 (:30)
  B9708; Trollope, Joanna; A Spanish Lover; 2/21/1997; 3/9/1997 (:24)
  B9709; Gustafson, Helen; The Agony Of The Leaves; 3/14/1997; 3/16/1997 (:30)
  B9710; Richburg, Keith; Out Of America - A Black Man Confronts Africa; 2/25/1997; 3/23/1997 (:15)
  B9710; Jarrard, Kyle; Over There; 3/3/1997; 3/23/1997 (:16)
  B9711; Buckley, Christopher; Wry Martinis; 3/17/1997; 3/30/1997 (:30)
  B9712; Chao, Patricia; Monkey King; 3/5/1997; 4/6/1997 (: 15)
  B9712; Ferguson, Gary; The Sylvan Path; 3/4/1997; 4/6/1997 (:15)
  B9713; Walters, Minette; The Echo; 3/28/1997; 4/13/1997 (:24)
  B9714; Leonard, John; Smoke And Mirrors; 3/25/1997; 4/20/1997 (:40)
  B9715; Lax, Eric; Bogart; 4/15/1997; 4/20/1997 (:25)
  B9716; Perry, Anne; Ashforth Hall; 4/1/1997; 4/27/1997 (:30)
  B9717; Leavitt, David; Arkansas; 4/15/1997; 5/4/1997 (:25)
  B9718; McMillan, Rosalyn; Knowing; 4/17/1997; 5/11/1997 (:15)
  B9718; Barnes, Linda; Cold Case; 4/10/1997; 5/11/1997 (:17)
  B9719; Signorile, Michaelangelo; Life Outside; 5/6/1997; 5/18/1997 (:25)
  B9720; Otto, Whitney; The Passion Dream Book; 5/2/1997; 5/25/1997 (:16)
  B9720; Taylor, Benjamin; Tales Out Of School; 4/14/1997; 5/25/1997 (:15)
  B9721; Bosworth, Patricia; Anything Your Little Heart Desires; 5/8/1997; 6/1/1997 (:15)
  B9721; Tuten, Frederic; Van Gogh's Bad Cafe; 3/19/1997; 6/1/1997(:15)
  B9722; Eberstadt, Fernanda; When The Sons Of Heaven Meet The Daughters Of The Earth; 4/10/1997; 6/8/1997 (:18)
  B9722; Cahill, Sarah; Desiring Italy; 5/20/1997; 6/8/1997 (:9)
  B9723; Wallace, James; Overdrive; 5/27/1997; 6/15/1997 (:17)
  B9723; Greenside, Mark; I Saw A Man Hit His Wife; 5/27/1997; 6/15/1997 (:10)
  B9724; Banville, John; The Untouchable; 5/13/1997; 6/22/1997 (:20)
  B9725; Stopfel, Barry & Leckie, Will; Courage To Love; 6/18/1997; 6/29/1997 (:30)
  B9726; McGowan, Chris; Make Your Own Dinosaur Out Of Chicken Bones; 6/6/1997; 7/6/1997 (:15)
  B9726; Cartwright, Gene; I Never Played Catch With My Father; 6/10/1997; 7/6/1997 (:14)
  B9727; Rutherfurd, Edward; London; 6/27/1997; 7/13/1997 (:22)
  B9728; Mayle, Peter; Chasing Cezanne; 6/27/1997; 7/20/1997 (:25)
  B9729; Phillips, Caryl; The Nature Of Blood; 6/10/1997; 7/27/1997 (:15)
  B9729; Delacorte, Peter; Time On My Hands; 6/9/1997; 7/27/1997 (:15)
  B9730; Fowler, Connie Mae; Before Women Had Wings; 5/28/1997; 8/3/1997 (:19)
  B9731; Goddard, Robert; Out Of The Sun; 6/30/1997; 8/10/1997 (:19)
  B9731; Carrozzi, Craig; The Road To El Dorado; 8/8/1997; 8/10/1997 (:09)
  B9732; Toibin, Colm; The Story of the Night; 5/8/1997; 8/17/1997 (:30)
  B9733; Liu, Aimee; Cloud Mountain; 7/14/1997; 8/24/1997 (:25)
  B9734; Barden, Dan; John Wayne - A Novel; 7/24/1997; 8/31/1997 (:17)
  B9734; Reynolds, Marjorie; The Starlite Drive-In; 8/7/1997; 8/31/1997 (:15)
  B9735; Lehane, Dennis; Sacred; 8/25/1997; 9/7/1997 (:24)
  B9736; Weltner, Peter; The Risk Of His Music; 9/3/1997; 9/14/1997 (:26)
  B9737; White, Edmund; The Farewell Symphony; 9/15/1997; 9/21/1997 (:30)
  B9738; Gadol, Peter; The Long Rain; 9/15/1997; 9/28/1997 (:11)
  B9738; Hoffman, Alice; Here On Earth; 9/9/1997; 9/28/1997 (:20)
  B9739; Gilboy, Peter; The Something Something; 9/26/1997; 10/5/1997 (:30)
  B9740; Powell, Kevin; Keepin' It Real; 9/26/1997; 10/12/1997 (:22)
  B9741; Smith, Bob; Openly Bob; 10/7/1997; 10/19/1997 (:25)
  B9743; Brown, Rita Mae; Rita Will; 10/10/1997; 11/2/1997 (:30)
  B9744; Geist, Bill; The Big Five-Oh; 10/3/1997; 11/9/1997 (:18)
  B9745; Kay, Terry; The Runaway; 10/24/1997; 11/16/1997 (:30)
  B9746; Rayner, Richard; Murder Book; 10/20/1997; 11/23/1997 (:30)
  B9747; Goodwin, Doris Kearns; Wait Till Next Year; 10/27/1997; 11/30/1997 (:30)
  B9748; Karnow, Stanley; Paris In The Fifties; 11/4/1997; 12/7/1997 (:24)
  B9749; Zimmerman, R. D.; Hostage; 11/4/1997; 12/14/1997 (:20)
  B9750; Gurganus, Allan; Plays Well With Others; 12/3/1997; 12/28/1997 (:30)
- 1998 Book Talk Episodes, 1997-1998; 27 audio cassettes tapes (Audio 2)
  Order of information: Episode Number; Author Last Name, Author First Name; Book Title; Record Date; Air Date (Length:Minutes)
  B9801; Cohen, Jaffe; The King Of Kings And I; 12/10/1997; 1/4/1998 (:26)
  B9802; Tune, Tommy; Footnotes; 11/5/1997; 1/11/1998 (:30)
  B9803; Alexie, Sherman; Indian Killer; 1/9/1998; 1/18/1998 Also Used On Open Air 2/23/98 (:23)
  B9804; Reed, Rita; Growing Up Gay; 1/14/1998; 1/25/1998 (:25)
  B9805; James; P. D.; A Certain Justice; 1/23/1998; 2/1/1998 (:30)
  B9806; Amis, Martin; Night Train; 1/27/1998; 2/8/1998 (:30)
  B9807; Purcell, Rosamond; Special Cases; 2/6/1998; 2/15/1998 (:20)
  B9808; Bornstein, Kate; My Gender Workbook; 2/12/1998; 2/22/1998 (:15)
  B9808; Baetz, Ruth; Wild Communion; 2/18/1998; 2/22/1998 (:14)
  B9809; Mann, William; Wisecracker; 2/25/1998; 3/1/1998 (:30)
  B9810; O'Donohue, John; Anam Cara - The Book Of Celtic Wisdom; 3/5/1998; 3/8/1998 (:26)
  B9811; Boyle, T. Coreghessan; Riven Rock; 3/4/1998; 3/15/1998 (:30)
  B9812; Gallagher, Hugh; Teeth; 3/5/1998; 3/22/1998 (:20)
  B9813; O'Faolain, Nuala; Are You Somebody; 3/20/1998; 3/29/1998 (:30)
  B9814; Spizer, Joyce; The Cop Was White As Snow; 3/20/1998; 4/5/1998 (:08)
  B9814; Savin-Williams, Ritch; And Then I Became Gay; 3/10/1998; 4/5/1998 (:20)
  B9815; Mah, Adeline Yen; Falling Leaves; 3/25/1998; 4/12/1998 (:14)
  B9816; Miller, Jon; Confessions of a Baseball Purist; 4/14/1998; 4/19/1998 (:30)
  B9817; Guinier, Lani; Lift Every Voice; 4/27/1998; 5/3/1998 (:24)
  B9818; Carlsson, Chris & Holloran, Pete; Reclaiming San Francisco; 4/9/1998; 5/3/1998 (:26)
  B9819; McGrath, Patrick; Asylum; 4/8/1998; 5/10/1998 (:30)
  B9820; Siegel, Susan & Siegel, David; Book Hunter's Guide to Used Book Stores - Pacific Coast; 4/13/1998; 5/17/1998 (:9)
  B9820; Gautreaux, Tim; The Next Step in the Dance; 4/6/1998; 5/17/1998 (:18)
  B9821; Ford, Richard; Women with Men; 5/11/1998; 5/24/1998 (:23)
  B9822; Holland, Merlin; The Wilde Album; 5/12/1998; 5/31/1998 (:30)
  B9823; Kennedy, Maxwell Taylor; Make Gentle the Life of the World; 5/14/1998; 6/7/1998 (:24)
  B9824; Wells, Rebecca; Divine Secrets of the Ya-Ya Sisterhood; 4/16/1998; 6/14/1998 (:24)
  B9825; Nunez, Sigrid; Mitz; 5/12/1998; 6/21/1998 (:15)
  B9825; Naylor, Gloria; The Men of Brewster Place; 6/1/1998; 6/21/1998 (:12)
  B9826; Barker, Clive; Galilee; 6/18/1998; 6/28/1998 (:30)
  B9827; Conway, Jill Ker; When Memory Speaks; 4/22/1998; 7/5/1998 (:24)
  B9828; Liu, Eric; The Accidental Asian; 6/11/1998; 7/12/1998 (:30)
  B9829; Atkins, Chloe; Girls Night Out; 6/30/1998; 7/19/1998 (:12)
  B9829; Hunter, Fred; Federal Fag; 6/19/1998; 7/19/1998 (:15)
  B9830; Fielding, Helen; Bridget Jones' Diary; 6/16/1998; 7/26/1998 (:24)
  B9831; Gomes, Peter; Sermons; 5/26/1998; 8/2/1998 (:24)
  B9832; Johnson, Charles; Dreamer; 5/7/1998; 8/9/1998 (:24)
  B9833; Labonte, Richard; A Different Light Bookstore; 8/10/1998; 8/16/1998 (:14)
  B9833; Ephron, Amy; A Cup of Tea; 6/30/1998; 8/16/1998 (:15)
  B9834; Woodbury, Marda; Stopping the Presses; 8/12/1998; 8/23/1998 (:22)
  B9834; Robinson, Peter; San Francisco Literary Society; 8/13/1998; 8/23/1998 (:07)
  B9835; Lehman, Godfrey; We the Jury; 8/18/1998; 8/30/1998 (:24)
  B9836; Leonard, Karen; American Way of Death; 8/20/1998; 9/6/1998 (:20)
  B9837; Wilson, Frank; The Hand; 9/10/1998; 9/13/1998 (:30)
  B9838; See, Lisa & Farmfarmanian, Roxane; Half and Half; 9/14/1998; 9/20/1998 (:30)
  B9839; Wick, Walter; Walter Wick's Optical Tricks; 9/18/1998; 9/27/1998 (:12)
  B9839; Smith, Julie; 82 Desire; 9/9/1998; 9/27/1998 (:16)
  B9840; Jackson, Brian Keith; Walking Through Mirrors; 9/28/1998; 10/4/1998 (:23)
  B9841; Djerassi, Carl; NO; 9/24/1998; 10/11/1998 (:25)
  B9842; Verghese, Abraham; The Tennis Partner; 9/30/1998; 10/18/1998 (:30)
  B9843; Lee, Gus; No Physical Evidence; 9/18/1998; 10/25/1998 (:16)
  B9844; Roszak, Theodore; America the Wise; 10/13/1998; 11/1/1998 (:23)
  B9845; Evans, Harold; The American Century; 10/28/1998; 11/1/1998 (:23)
  B9846; Solway, Diane; Nureyev; 10/21/1998; 11/8/1998 (:30)
  B9847; Patterson, Richard North; No Safe Place; 9/28/1998; 11/8/1998 (:22)
  B9848; Singh, Simon; Fermat's Enigma; 10/26/1998; 11/15/1998 (:30)
  B9849; Fox, Laurie; My Sister from the Black Lagoon; 9/25/1998; 11/22/1998 (:23)
  B9850; Choi, Susan; The Foreign Student; 9/23/1998; 11/29/1998 (:19)
  B9851; Isaacs, Susan; Red, White and Blue; 10/27/1998; 12/6/1998 (:24)
  B9852; Wasserman, Fred; Becoming Visible; 11/30/1998; 12/13/1998 (:30)
  B9853; Cady, Barbara; Icons of the Twentieth Century; 12/11/1998; 12/20/1998 (:30)
  B9854; Masumoto, David Mas; Harvest Son; 10/7/1998; 12/27/1998 (:20)
- 1999 Book Talk Episodes, 1998-1999; 24 audio cassette tapes (Audio 3)
  B9901; Nachman, Gerald; Raised by Radio; 12/16/1998; 1/3/1999 (:30)
  B9902; Day, Barry; Noel Coward - The Complete Lyrics; 12/17/1998; 1/10/1999 (:12)
  B9902; Polt, Renata; A Thousand Kisses; 1/5/1999; 1/10/1999 (:15)
  B9903; Bono, Chastity; Family Outing; 10/21/1998; 1/17/1999 (:20)
  B9904; McCabe, Patrick; Breakfast on Pluto; 1/22/1999; 1/24/1999 (:30)
  B9905; Stahl, Lesley; Reporting Live; 1/25/1999; 1/31/1999 (:30)
  B9906; Guralnick, Peter; Careless Love - The Unmaking of Elvis Presley; 1/27/1999; 2/7/1999 (:30)
  B9907; Belart, Luis; Sugan Busters; 2/1/1999; 2/14/1999 (:21)
  B9908; McEwan, Ian; Amsterdam; 2/1/1999; 2/21/1999 (:30)
  B9909; Hertsgaard, Mark; Earth Odyssey; 1/28/1999; 2/28/1999 (:27)
  B9910; Greene, Brian; Elegant Universe; 2/5/1999; 3/7/1999 (:24)
  B9911; Whitehead, Colson; The Intuitionist; 2/3/1999; 3/14/1999 (:21)
  B9912; Middlebrook, Diane; Suits Me; 2/11/1999; 3/21/1999 (:30)
  B9913; Louganis, Greg; For the Life of Your Dog; 2/19/1999; 3/28/1999 (:30)
  B9914; Garland, Alex; The Tesseract; 3/5/1999; 4/4/1999 (:30)
  B9915; Kline, Christina Baker; Desire Lines; 2/10/1999; 4/11/1999 (:24)
  B9916; Stephanopoulos, George; All Too Human - A Political Education; 4/5/1999; 4/18/1999 (:30)
  B9917; DeGeneres, Betty; Love, Ellen - A Mother/Daughter Journey; 4/7/1999; 5/2/1999 (:26)
  B9918; Podhoretz, Norman; Ex Friends; 4/8/1999; 5/9/1999 (:30)
  B9919; Indiana, Gary; Three Month Fever; 4/20/1999; 5/16/1999 (:22)
  B9920; Hijuelos, Oscar; Empress of the Splendid Season; 2/18/1999; 5/23/1999 (:30)
  B9921; Bloch, Chana; Mrs Dumpty; 5/12/1999; 5/30/1999 (:15)
  B9921; Baker, Kevin; Dreamland; 3/11/1999; 5/30/1999 (:12)
  B9922; Rushdie, Salman; The Ground Beneath Her Feet; 5/6/1999; 6/6/1999 (:30)
  B9923; Wagner, Gottfried; Twilight of the Wagners; 5/26/1999; 6/13/1999 (:30)
  B9924; Mazursky, Paul; Show Me the Magic; 6/7/1999; 6/20/1999 (:30)
  B9925; Seth, Vikram; An Equal Music; 5/18/1999; 6/27/1999 (:30)
  B9926; Bryson, Bill; I'm a Stranger Here Myself; 5/24/1999; 7/4/1999 (:30)
  B9927; Mason, Richard; The Drowning People; 5/25/1999; 7/11/1999 (:30)
  B9928; Clendinen, Dudley; Out for Good; 6/15/1999; 7/18/1999 (:30)
  B9929; Sheridan, Peter; 44 Dublin Made Me; 5/14/1999; 7/25/1999 (:30)
  B9930; Greenlaw, Linda; The Hungry Ocean; 5/17/1999; 8/1/1999 (:23)
  B9931; Channer, Colin; Waiting in Vain; 7/7/1999; 8/8/1999 (:30)
  B9932; Paley, Maggie; The Book of the Penis; 7/9/1999; 8/15/1999 (:21)
  B9933; Williams, Niall; As It Is in Heaven; 7/22/1999; 8/22/1999 (:30)
  B9934; Darnton, John; The Experiment; 8/20/1999; 8/29/1999 (:30)
  B9935; Cannell, Dorothy; The Trouble with Harriett; 5/18/1999; 9/5/1999 (:15)
  B9935; De La Huerta, Christian; Coming Out Spiritually; 9/1/1999; 9/5/1999 (:14)
  B9936; Gerritsen, Tess; Gravity; 9/10/1999; 9/19/1999 (:23)
  B9937; Lee, Chang-Rae; A Gesture Life; 9/14/1999; 9/26/1999 (:30)
  B9938; Ross, Andrew; The Celebration Chronicles; 9/17/1999; 10/3/1999 (:24)
  B9939; Feiffer, Jules; Bark, George; 9/29/1999; 10/10/1999 (:30)
  B9940; Lemann, Nicholas; The Big Test; 10/6/1999; 10/17/1999 (:22)
  B9941; Doyle, Roddy; A Star Called Henry; 10/1/1999; 10/17/1999 (:30)
  B9942; Frayn, Michael; Headlong; 10/4/1999; 10/24/1999 (:40)
  B9943; Soukhanov, Anne; Enacrta World English Dictionary; 9/17/1999; 10/31/1999 (:23)
  B9944; Yost, Merle; When Love Lasts Forever; 10/5/1999; 11/7/1999 (:24)
  B9945; Dunne, Dominic; The Way We Lived Then; 10/18/1999; 11/14/1999 (:30)
  B9946; Vreeland, Susan; Girl in Hyacinth Blue; 9/24/1999; 11/21/1999 (:14)
  B9946; Landvik, Lorna; Tall Pine Polka; 9/22/1999; 11/21/1999 (:16)
  B9947; Watson, Jeanette; Bookstore; 10/14/1999; 11/28/1999 (:30)
  B9948; Zimmerman, R. D.; Innuendo; 11/17/1999; 12/5/1999 (:18)
- 2000 Book Talk Episodes, 25 audio cassette tapes (Audio 4)
  B0001; Dearborn, Mary; Mailer; 1/13/2000; 1/16/2000 (:22)
  B0002; Stein, Edward; The Mismeasure of Desire; 1/19/2000; 1/23/2000 (:30)
  B0003; Findley, Timothy; Pilgrim; 1/28/2000; 1/30/2000 (:30)
  B0004; Toobin, Jeffrey; A Vast Conspiracy; 1/26/2000; 2/6/2000 (:30)
  B0005; Thubron, Colin; In Siberia; 2/7/2000; 2/13/2000 (:30)
  B0006; D'Erasmo, Stacey; Tea; 2/16/2000; 2/20/2000 (:23)
  B0007; Mosley, Walter; Workin' on the Chain Gang; 2/23/2000; 2/27/2000 (:25)
  B0008; Spong, John Shelby; Here I Stand; 2/28/2000; 3/5/2000 (:30)
  B0009; Merling, Andrew; The Wedding; Wythe; Douglas; 2/28/2000; 3/12/2000 (:30)
  B0010; Troupe, Quincy; Miles and Me; 3/8/2000; 3/19/2000 (:30)
  B0011; Murray, William; Janet, My Mother and Me; 3/15/2000; 3/26/2000 (:30)
  B0012; Reidenbach, Michael; Legacy and Destiny; Renkowski; Dane; 3/31/2000; 4/2/2000 (:30)
  B0013; Jones, Cleve; Stitching a Revolution; 4/3/2000; 4/9/2000 (:30)
  B0014; Cairns, David; Berlioz; 4/10/2000; 4/16/2000 (:30)
  B0015; O'Connell, Brian; Civil Society; 4/12/2000; 4/23/2000 (:24)
  B0016; Prose, Francine; Blue Angel; 4/26/2000; 4/30/2000 (:30)
  B0017; Laurents, Arthur; Original Story By; 4/7/2000; 5/7/2000 (:30)
  B0018; Laurents, Arthur; Original Story By (Part 2 Of 2); 4/7/2000; 5/14/2000 (:30)
  B0019; Oates, Joyce Carol; Blonde; 5/3/2000; 5/21/2000 (:30)
  B0020; Lanchester, John; Mr. Phillips; 4/26/2000; 5/28/2000 (:30)
  B0021; Fitzgerald, Frances; Way Out There in the Blue; 5/9/2000; 6/4/2000 (:30)
  B0022; Friedan, Betty; Life So Far; 5/16/2000; 6/11/2000 (:30)
  B0023; Seth, Vikram; An Equal Music (II); 5/15/2000; 6/18/2000 (:30)
  B0024; Alexie, Sherman; The Toughest Indian in the World; 5/23/2000; 6/25/2000 (:30)
  B0025; Clark, Mary Higgins; Before I Say Goodbye; 5/30/2000; 7/2/2000 (:30)
  B0026; Schell, Orville; Virtual Tibet; 6/23/2000; 7/9/2000 (:30)
  B0027; Crais, Robert; Demolition Angel; 6/2/2000; 7/16/2000 (:30)
  B0028; White, Edmund; The Married Man; 6/9/2000; 7/23/2000 (:30)
  B0029; MacLeod, Alistair; No Great Mischief; 6/2/2000; 7/30/2000 (:30)
  B0030; Bryson, Bill; In a Sunburned Country; 6/14/2000; 8/6/2000 (:30)
  B0031; Lynch, Thomas; Bodies in Motion and at Rest; 6/15/2000; 8/13/2000 (:30)
  B0032; Nasaw, David; The Chief; 6/28/2000; 8/20/2000 (:30)
  B0033; Leffland, Ella; Breath and Shadow; 7/6/2000; 8/27/2000 (:24)
  B0034; Beaton, M. C.; The Fairies of Fryfam; 7/17/2000; 9/3/2000 (:30)
  B0035; Provenzano, Jim; PINS; 8/15/2000; 9/10/2000 (:30)
  B0036; Brookes, Tim; Hell of a Place to Lose a Cow; 7/18/2000; 9/17/2000 (:30)
  B0037; Burke, James Lee; Purple Cane Road; 8/7/2000; 9/24/2000 (:25)
  B0038; Reichs, Kathy; Deadly Decisions; 8/15/2000; 10/1/2000 (:30)
  B0039; Sherwood, Ben; The Man Who Ate the 747; 9/12/2000; 10/8/2000 (:24)
  B0040; Gergen, David; Eyewitness to Power; 9/28/2000; 10/15/2000 (:30)
  B0041; Maupin, Armistead; The Night Listener; 9/27/2000; 10/22/2000 (:30)
  B0042; Bantock, Nick; The Artful Dodger; 9/26/2000; 10/29/2000 (:30)
  B0043; Soenlein, Karl M.; The World of Normal Boys; 9/22/2000; 11/5/2000 (:30)
  B0044; Hearn, Michael Patrick; The Annotated Wizard of Oz; 9/27/2000; 11/12/2000 (:30)
  B0045; Leonard, Elmore; Pagan Babies; 9/28/2000; 11/19/2000 (:30)
  B0046; Ishiguro, Kazuo; When We Were Orphans; 10/8/2000; 11/26/2000 (:32)
  B0047; Perry, Anne; Slaves of Obsession; 10/10/2000; 12/3/2000 (:30)
  B0048; Lightman, Alan; The Diagnosis; 10/19/2000; 12/10/2000 (:25)
  B0049; Wylie, Peter; National Trust Guide to San Francisco; 10/31/2000; 12/24/2000 (:30)
- 2001 Book Talk Episodes, 2000-2001; 25 audio cassette tapes (Audio 5)
  B0101; Holland, Merlin; The Complete Letters of Oscar Wilde; 11/21/2000; 1/7/2001 (:23)
  B0102; Carr, Caleb; Killing Time; 12/1/2000; 1/14/2001 (:25)
  B0103; Stark, Elizabeth; Shy Girl; 12/21/2000; 1/21/2001 (:25)
  B0104; Kershaw, Ian; Hitler: 1936-1945 Nemesis; 1/18/2001; 1/28/2001 (:30)
  B0105; Chevalier, Tracy; Girl with a Pearl Earring; 1/25/2001; 2/11/2001 (:30)
  B0106; Suri, Manil; The Death of Vishnu; 2/5/2001; 2/18/2001 (:30)
  B0107; White, Edmund; Loss within Loss; 2/12/2001; 2/25/2001 (:30)
  B0108; Walker, Rebecca; Black White and Jewish; 2/14/2001; 3/4/2001 (:30)
  B0109; Giddins, Gary; Bing Crosby; 2/16/2001; 3/11/2001 (:30)
  B0110; Durham, David Anthony; Gabriel's Story; 2/23/2001; 3/18/2001 (:30)
  B0111; MacLeod, Alistair; Island; 2/26/2001; 3/25/2001 (:30)
  B0112; Carey, Peter; True History of the Kelly Gang; 3/8/2001; 4/1/2001 (:30)
  B0113; Schneider, Bart; Secret Love; 3/15/2001; 4/8/2001 (:24)
  B0114; McCabe, Patrick; Emerald Germs of Ireland; 3/12/2001; 4/15/2001 (:30)
  B0115; O'Faolain, Nuala; My Dream of You; 3/23/2001; 4/22/2001 (:30)
  B0116; MacDonald, Hector; Mind Game; 3/5/2001; 4/29/2001 (:30)
  B0117; Wilson, Cintra; A Massive Swelling; 3/15/2001; 5/6/2001 (:30)
  B0118; Mieville, China; Perdido Street Station; 3/22/2001; 5/13/2001 (:23)
  B0119; Ong, Han; Fixer Chao; 5/2/2001; 5/20/2001 (:30)
  B0120; Garfield, Simon; Mauve; 4/23/2001; 5/27/2001 (:24)
  B0121; Bach, Steven; Dazzler; 5/9/2001; 6/3/2001 (:30)
  B0122; Canin, Ethan; Carry Me Across the Water; 5/18/2001; 6/17/2001 (:30)
  B0123; Brechin, Gray; Imperial San Francisco; 4/4/2001; 6/10/2001 (:30)
  B0124; Ryan, Terry; The Prize Winner of Defiance, Ohio; 5/22/2001; 6/24/2001 (:22)
  B0125; Houston, James; Snow Mountain Passage; 4/19/2001; 7/1/2001 (:30)
  B0126; Grafton, Sue; P is for Peril; 6/18/2001; 7/8/2001 (:30)
  B0127; James, P. D.; Death in Holy Orders; 5/4/2001; 7/15/2001 (:30)
  B0128; McCullough, David; John Adams; 6/18/2001; 7/22/2001 (:30)
  B0129; Rakoff, David; Fraud; 6/12/2001; 7/29/2001 (:30)
  B0130; Whitehead, Colson; John Henry Days; 6/12/2001; 8/5/2001 (:23)
  B0131; Wasserstein, Wendy; Shiksa Goddess; 6/15/2001; 8/12/2001 (:25)
  B0132; Patchett, Ann; Bel Canto; 6/20/2001; 8/19/2001 (:30)
  B0133; Mosley, Walter; Fearless Jones; 7/13/2001; 8/26/2001 (:30)